bargainbrute.com 2019-03-31

# HUGE Online Shopping Mall - See our Shopping Deals of the Day

#### Privacy

Your privacy as a visitor at BargainBrute is important to us, which is why we pay special attention to your privacy as well as the confidentiality of your personal data. Just like all the best online shopping websites, we want to make sure that you understand our privacy policy, which is why we are sharing this policy usage with you, so you can better understand our online information practices. 

When you visit our website, you are required to provide us your personal information, including your name, address, contact number, as well as credit card information, so that we can process your order. The information you share is safe with us, and is not shared with outside parties other than the companies that we have outsourced our functions to. Limited data is presented to them, in order to make sure that you get optional marketing assistance. 

The information you provide us, helps us in processing your orders, verify your account, as well as in communicating with you regarding your online orders. Your personal information can be assessed and updated from the profile page, and you can update the information anytime you want. 

It is important you know that BargainBrute has the right to modify the privacy policy at any time, so you are requested to review it regularly. If any changes are made to this policy, you will be notified via email or a notice at the homepage of our website. 

If you have any questions, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.bargainbrute.com/catalog/contactus).
